RAHUL BHARTI () Featured

Android Developer seeking roles in Project Management, Software Development, Resource Management, Process Enhancement, Productivity Enhancement, Client Engagement, Coding, Design, Requirement Analysis, Configuration, Documentation



Current Designation: Android Developer Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: .kreate Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Noida Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Noida, Bengaluru / Bangalore, Gurgaon Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Key Skills: Android Developer, Software Developer, Project Management, Software Development, Resource Management, Process Enhancement, Productivity Enhancement, Client Engagement, Coding, Design, Requirement

Analysis, Configuration, Documentation

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

MCA and achievement-oriented professional, offering a career of nearly 3 years in Application Development (Android Platform) Skills in mapping business requirements, designing customized solutions with strong analytical skills and capability to analyze business practices and define optimal procedures

Experience in the Software Development Lifecycle (SDLC) right from requirement analysis, documentation (functional specifications, technical design), coding and testing (preparation of test cases along with implementation) to maintenance of proposed applications

Expertise in using Kotlin and Java Technologies for Mobile Applications

Rich experience of working with customers, project managers and technical teams for securing & executing concurrent projects; envisioning usage of new technology and tailoring its usage for achieving desired results

Work Experience

.kreate as Android Developer Dec 2020 to Till Date

implement coding and design as per the requirement.

railyatri.in as Technical Specialist Jul 2019 to Jul 2020

My role in this company is that implementation code and create design behalf on requirement, Give the opione on the app how app would be grow in the market, Create strategy on app and descuss with team lead along with manager.

RailYatri.in as Android Developer Jul 2019 to Jul 2020

railyatri.in as Technical Specialist Android Developer Jul 2019 to Jul 2020

as Technical Specialist Jul 2019 to Jul 2020

1/22/2021

Railyatri.in as Technical Specialist Jul 2019 to Jul 2020

Ndinfotech Pvt. Ltd as Android Developer Jul 2017 to Jul 2019

Education

UG: BCA (Computers) from I.A.S.E Deemed University, Rajasthan in 2013

PG: MCA (Computers) from Kamla Nehru Institute of Technology, Sultanpur UP in 2017

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version | Last Used | Experience |
|--|---------|-----------|------------|
| Kotlin and Java Technologies | | | |
| Remote Config (A/B Testing), Analytics | | | |
| Stripe, PayUMoney | | | |
| Xml/Json Parsing | | | |

Languages Known

| Language | Proficiency | Read | Write | Speak |
|----------|-------------|------|-------|-------|
| English | | | | |
| Hindi | | | | |

Affirmative Action

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Category: General

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization